camosun.ca 2008-04-14

# Website Privacy Statement - Camosun College

Lansdowne campus map  
3100 Foul Bay Rd  
Victoria BC, V8P 5J2

Interurban campus map  
4461 Interurban Rd  
Victoria BC, V9E 2C1

**Main Switchboard:** 250-370-3000

**Information & Registration**  
**Phone:** 250–370–3550  
**Toll free:** 1–877–554–7555  
**Email:**[info@camosun.bc.ca](mailto:info@camosun.bc.ca)

## Hours

**Information & Registration Hours**
    Mon – Wed 9 am – 4 pm   
Thur 9 am – 5:30 pm  
Fri 9 am – 4 pm 
Assessment Hours
Academic Advising Hours
Cashiers Hours
Financial Aid and Awards Hours
Disability Resources Hours
Library Hours

Camosun College respects the privacy of personal information and strives to maintain the public’s trust through transparency and accountability in its use of personal information.  Personal information is information which can be used to distinguish, identify, or contact an individual specifically and which is not publicly available.

This website exists to benefit the Camosun community, its supporters, and the public. Use is free and anonymous except where sign-in is required. If you choose to send us personal information you consent to its collection and use by the College.

The personal information you provide may be used by the College to correspond with you, for registration, to process a donation, for surveys, and for other purposes that are consistent with the purpose for which the information was provided.  The College may share this information with the College Foundation and its Alumni Association.  The College will not disclose personal information you provide to any other third party without your permission unless required to do so by law.  All personal information is protected in accordance with the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act. 

To provide effective website search results, camosun.ca sends information anonymously to google.com. This information is used only for statistical purposes with no personally identifiable information sent. 

Our password protocols and encryption software are routinely updated to maximize protection of personal and other information. While we strive to protect personal information, please note that no Internet data transmission is completely secure.

This policy is regularly reviewed and updated to reflect our practices.
